[
  {
    "title": "Addition for kids - Learning to add with Dinosaurs",
    "src": "../math/v1.mp4",
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "5"],
        "correct": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 3 + 3?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "7"],
        "correct": "6"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 1 + 4?",
        "options": ["4", "5", "6"],
        "correct": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 5 + 3?",
        "options": ["6", "7", "8"],
        "correct": "8"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 2 + 3?",
        "options": ["4", "5", "6"],
        "correct": "5"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Addition exercises for kids - Learn to add with Dino",
    "src": "../math/v2.mp4",
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is 5 + 5?",
        "options": ["3", "8", "10"],
        "correct": "10"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 4 + 2?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "7"],
        "correct": "6"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 3 + 1?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "5"],
        "correct": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 6 + 3?",
        "options": ["7", "8", "9"],
        "correct": "9"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 2 +0?",
        "options": ["2", "4", "3"],
        "correct": "2"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Addition exercises for kids - Learn to add with Dino with burgers",
    "src": "../math/v3.mp4",
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is 5 - 2?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "2"],
        "correct": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 4 + 2?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "7"],
        "correct": "6"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 3 + 2?",
        "options": ["4", "5", "6"],
        "correct": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 7 - 5?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3"],
        "correct": "2"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 1 + 5?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "7"],
        "correct": "6"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Subtractions for kids - Learn to subtract with Dinosaurs - Mathematics for kids",
    "src": "../math/v4.mp4",
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is 5 - 2?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "2"],
        "correct": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 4 - 1?",
        "options": ["2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 3 - 2?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3"],
        "correct": "1"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 7 - 4?",
        "options": ["2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 6 - 3?",
        "options": ["2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": "3"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Subtraction exercises for kids - Learn to subtract with Dino and Saury",
    "src": "../math/v5.mp4",
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is 5 - 2?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "2"],
        "correct": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 4 + 2?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "7"],
        "correct": "6"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 8 - 3?",
        "options": ["4", "5", "6"],
        "correct": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 6 - 1?",
        "options": ["4", "5", "6"],
        "correct": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 7 - 5?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3"],
        "correct": "2"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Addition for kids - Mathematics for kids with dinosaurs - Exercises",
    "src": "../math/v6.mp4",
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is 1 + 1?",
        "options": ["2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": "2"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "5"],
        "correct": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 3 + 3?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "7"],
        "correct": "6"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 5 + 0?",
        "options": ["4", "5", "6"],
        "correct": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 4 + 2?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "7"],
        "correct": "6"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Subtraction exercises - Learn to subtract with Dinosaurs",
    "src": "../math/v7.mp4",
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is 6 - 2?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "5"],
        "correct": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 8 - 5?",
        "options": ["2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 10 - 6?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "5"],
        "correct": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 7 - 4?",
        "options": ["2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 9 - 3?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "7"],
        "correct": "6"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Subtraction for kids - Learn how to subtract",
    "src": "../math/v8.mp4",
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "What is 7 - 3?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "5"],
        "correct": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 10 - 5?",
        "options": ["4", "5", "6"],
        "correct": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 8 - 2?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "7"],
        "correct": "6"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 9 - 4?",
        "options": ["4", "5", "6"],
        "correct": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 6 - 2?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "5"],
        "correct": "4"
      }
    ]
  }
]
